A Guide to the A Guide to the Arena Stage Printed Press Items, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University Libraries
A Guide to the Arena Stage Printed Press Items 1950-2000
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University Libraries
Arena 0021
107 containers, 37 cubic feet (55.5 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired from Arena Stage in 2006.
Biographical Information
Arena Stage was an early leader in the resident theater movement. One of the first not-for-profit theaters in the United States as well as a pioneer of the regional theater movement the Arena Stage was the first regional theater to transfer a production to Broadway, the first invited by the U.S. State Department to tour behind the Iron Curtain and the first to receive a Tony Award. Co-founded in 1950 by Edward Mangum a teacher from the George Washington University, and Zelda Fichandler one of his students, Arena Stage was opened in Washington D.C. to fill the void left by the closing of the National Theater in 1948. Deriving it's name from the idea of "theater in the round," Arena Stage became one of the first resident theaters in the United States, beginning with a company of only eight actors. Today, Arena performs to over 250,000 patrons during a September to June season and employs nearly 200 theater professionals and craft persons, who are responsible for all the costumes and scenery seen on stage. Many now- famous actors took part in Arena Stage productions during the early part of their careers. Some of them include Robert Prosky, Morgan Freeman, Dianne Weist, James Earl Jones, Kevin Kline, Christopher Guest, Yeardly Smith and Samuel L. Jackson. Donated to George Mason University in fall of 2000, the Arena Stage Collection contains materials spanning the theater's 50 year history including production notebooks, photographs, playbills, scrapbooks, scripts and handwritten correspondence and other production materials.
Scope and Content
The Collection contains printed materials including: promotional brochures and postcards, invitations, fund raising mailings, press clippings and reviews of Arena Stage productions, programs for Arena Stage productions, immigration materials for foreign born actors and other miscellaneous items.
Arrangement
Collection is arranged by production title and type of material.
Contents List
- Arena Stage: Printed Press Coverage
  Contains press articles, reviews, press releases,brochures and other Misc. material related to Arena Stage productions.
  - "Curse of the Starving Class" (Box Box 1)
  - "Gymbeline" (Box Box 1)
  - "Dead Souls" (Box Box 1)
  - "Dear Janet Rosenber, Dear Mr. Kooning and Jakey Fat Boy" (Box Box 1)
  - "Dear Liar" (Box Box 1)
  - "Dear Nobody" (Box Box 1)
  - "Death and the King's Horseman" (Box Box 1)
  - "Dangerous Corner" (Box Box 1)
  - "Danton's Death" (Box Box 1)
  - "Dark of the Moon" (Box Box 1)
  - "Das Lusitania Songspiel" (Box Box 1)
  - "A Day in Hollywood/ A Night in the Ukraine" (Box Box 1)
  - "Days of Absence" (Box Box 1)
  - "Dandelion Wine" (1 of 3) (Box Box 1)
  - "Dandelion Wine" (2 of 3) (Box Box 1)
  - "Dandelion Wine" (3 of 3) (Box Box 1)
  - "Dance of Death" (Box Box 1)
  - "Dancers" (Box Box 1)
  - Printed pieces (Box Box 2)
  - Printed pieces (Box Box 2)
  - Printed Pieces (Box Box 2)
  - The Coconuts (Box Box 3)
  - A Dole House (Box Box 1)
  - Don Juan (Box Box 3)
  - Disability: A Comedy Carousel of New Plays (Box Box 3)
  - Dream Engine (Box Box 3)
  - In the Process Play - Desert Dwellers (Box Box 3)
  - In the Process Play - Disability (Box Box 3)
  - Emigres (Box Box 3)
  - Haiti (1 of 2) (Box Box 4)
  - Haiti (2 of 2) (Box Box 4)
  - Interview with Louis Lantz (Box Box 4)
  - Lantz, Louis (Box Box 4)
  - Transcripts (Box Box 4)
  - "T. Buttita" (Box Box 4)
  - "Interview with Mr. Davidson" (Box Box 4)
  - "Hyperion" (Box Box 4)
  - The Forever Child (Box Box 4)
  - Subscription material 1991 - 1992 (Box Box 5)
  - Before it Hits Home (Box Box 5)
  - Closer Than Ever (Box Box 5)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle (Box Box 5)
  - The Seagull (Box Box 5)
  - Open House Postcards (Box Box 5)
  - Expect the Unexpected (Box Box 5)
  - Sub-Ticket Exchange forms (Box Box 5)
  - She Stoops to Conquer (Box Box 5)
  - On the Way Home (Box Box 5)
  - Pygmalion (Box Box 5)
  - 40th Anniversary (Box Box 5)
  - Our Town (Box Box 5)
  - On-Stage at Arena Stage (Box Box 5)
  - ASA Archives (1 of 2) (Box Box 5)
  - ASA Archives (2 of 2) (Box Box 5)
  - Touring Press Clips (USSR and H.K.) (Box Box 6)
  - Brochures, invitations, etc... (Box Box 6)
  - Development (Box Box 6)
  - Callboard and Alumni Review (Box Box 6)
  - ASA materials (Box Box 6)
  - Season Materials 1975-1986 (Box Box 7)
  - Living Stage Materials (Box Box 7)
  - Development [Materials] (Box Box 7)
  - Individual Production Fliers (Box Box 7)
  - Flyers 1957-1973 (Box Box 7)
  - Saturday Review, March 27, 1971 (Box Box 7)
  - American Theatre (April 1985) and Guide to the Arts (May, 1978) (Box Box 7)
  - Washingtonian (Oct. 1970) and Amepnka (1975) (Box Box 7)
  - America's Arena and A Permanent Theatre Home (Box Box 7)
  - Richard Bryan - letters 1982/1983 season archives (Box Box 8)
  - Annual Report Working file 1984-1985 season (Box Box 8)
  - Wayne's Cultural Diversity / multiracial casting (Box Box 8)
  - Misc. production brochures (Box Box 9)
  - Misc. brochures (Box Box 9)
  - Misc. Brochures (Box Box 9)
  - Misc. Brochures (Box Box 9)
  - Programs (1 of 2) (Box Box 10)
  - Arena Stage letterhead (Box Box 10)
  - Press Releases (Box Box 10)
  - Production Showtimes (Box Box 10)
  - Misc. brochures, reports, play bills (Box Box 10)
  - Misc. brochures, playbills, etc. (Box Box 10)
  - Misc. brochures (Box Box 10)
  - Misc. brochures (Box Box 10)
  - Misc. Brochures, flyers, etc... (Box Box 11)
  - 1950 Arena Box Office report (Box Box 11)
  - General Articles 1970-1979 (Box Box 11)
  - General Articles 76/77 (Box Box 11)
  - General Articles 77/78 (Box Box 11)
  - General Articles 78/79 (Box Box 11)
  - General Articles 80/81 (Box Box 11)
  - General Articles 81/82 (Box Box 11)
  - General Articles 82/83 (Box Box 11)
  - General Articles 83/84 (Box Box 11)
  - Misc. Brochures (Box Box 11)
  - Misc. Brochures (Box Box 11)
  - Misc. materials from late 70's to early 80's (Box Box 11)
  - Periodicals and Journal Articles 1970's - 1980's (Box Box 12)
  - Washington Post advertising (Box Box 12)
  - Handicap materials (Box Box 12)
  - Theatre profiles 1980 (Box Box 12)
  - Arena Stage Associates Listing insert and "The 1940's Radio Hour" program (Box Box 12)
  - Tintypes - A Ragtime Revue (Box Box 12)
  - Group Sales/ Stationary and Teibele ASA Listings (Box Box 12)
  - Associates (Box Box 12)
  - Realtor's Subscription Brochure Package 1979 (Box Box 12)
  - Mummenschanz stuffer (Box Box 12)
  - 10K "Fund" Run sign up sheet (Box Box 12)
  - Theatre Profiles / 1978 (Box Box 12)
  - "In the Process" Programs 1978 (Box Box 12)
  - 30th Anniversary Season (Box Box 12)
  - Golden Circle and Student subscription series (Box Box 12)
  - Flyers and Inserts 1977-1978 (Box Box 12)
  - Giant Food Associates Night flyer, "A Winter's Tale" (Box Box 12)
  - Arena Stage Associates (Box Box 12)
  - Theatre Profiles 1978 (Box Box 12)
  - Photos (Box Box 12)
  - Misc. flyers and invitations (Box Box 12)
  - America's Arena and Saturday Review (Box Box 12)
  - Invitation, "Conquest of the South Pole" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "Fences" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "A Doll House" (March 7th) (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "A Doll House" (March 8th) (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "Merrily we Roll Along" (Feb. 7th) (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "Merrily we Roll Along" (Feb. 1st) (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "Montieth and Rand" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "The man who came to dinner" (Box Box 13)
  - invitation, "Stand up Tragedy" (Jan. 18th) (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "Stand up Tragedy" (Jan. 17th) (Box Box 13)
  - Letters to subscribers about special performance of "Montieth and Rand" (Box Box 13)
  - Playbill, "Conquest of the South Pole" (Box Box 13)
  - Press Release, "Pygmalion" (Feb. 25, 1991) (Box Box 13)
  - Press Release, "Pygmalion" (Feb. 13, 1991) (Box Box 13)
  - Press Release, "Born Guilty" and Before it hits Home" (Jan. 25, 1991) (Box Box 13)
  - Brochure, "Standup Tragedy" (Jan. 12 - Feb. 18 no year) (Box Box 13)
  - Brochure, "On the way Home" June 2 - July 2, 1989 (Box Box 13)
  - Post Card, George Kaufman's 100th birthday celebration, Dec. 10, 1989 (Box Box 13)
  - postcard, signature series, March 11, 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Motieth and Rand" Dec. 12 - Jan. 7th (no year) (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, Signature Series, Feb. 4th 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, Signature Series, Oct. 29, 1989 (Box Box 13)
  - Playbill, "Fences", April 20 - July 8, 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Brochure, "On the Way Home" 1989-1990 season (Box Box 13)
  - Brochure, Group Sales (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Juno and the Paycock" May 4 - June 10 (no year) (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Merrily we Roll Along" Jan. 26 - April 8 (no year) (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, Season's Greetings discount offer, Dec. 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Merrily we Roll Along", Jan. 26 - April 8 (no year) (Box Box 13)
  - Press Release, "On the Town" (Box Box 13)
  - On Stage, Vol. 1 No. 1 (1989 - 1990) (Box Box 13)
  - On Stage, Vol. 1, No. 2 (Box Box 13)
  - Brochure, A Stage Four Workshop, Jan. 22 - 24, 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Donation Card, George Kaufman 100th Birthday, Nov. 16, 1989 (Box Box 13)
  - Company Letter, Living Stage Theatre (Box Box 13)
  - 40-Year Celebration save 20% letter (Box Box 13)
  - Brochure, congressional ticket hotline (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation, "Juno and Paycock" May 9 - 10, 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, seasons greetings 1-% discount (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "The Glass Menagerie" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Fences" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Merrily we Roll Along" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "A Dolls House" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "A Doll House" March 8th (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Stand-up Tragedy" Jan. 18th (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Conqest of the South Pole" March 21st. (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Stand-up Tragedy", Jan. 17th. (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Fences" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Merrily we Roll Along" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Montieth and Rand" (Box Box 13)
  - Coupon, "On the Way Home" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitations, "Fences" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitations, "The Man who can to Dinner" (Box Box 13)
  - subscription info 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - 40th Anniversary envelopes 1990 - 1991 (Box Box 13)
  - 3 play package holiday special, 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - Cross Currents, 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - Seasonal Announcements 1990 - 1991 (Box Box 13)
  - Subscription order form (Box Box 13)
  - Coupon promotion (Box Box 13)
  - Five Play Promotional Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - Subscription Forms for the 1989-1990 season (Box Box 13)
  - Emergency Campaign to Save the Arts Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - 2 Show Holiday Package Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - 3 Play Package Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - National VIP theatre hotline card (Box Box 13)
  - 1989-1990 Season Schedule Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - Promotional Letter for Triple Play series (Box Box 13)
  - "The Proposal" (Box Box 13)
  - Subscription ticket exchange card (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Juno and the Paycock" (Box Box 13)
  - Discount letters to subscribers for "Montieth and Rand" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Mr. Ibsen Speaks!!!" April 1, 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Internship Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - Program book/restaurant guide 1988-1989 season (Box Box 13)
  - 1989-1990 season, Sept. - June Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - "A Midsummer Night's Dream", invite/response card (1989-1990) (Box Box 13)
  - "The Glass Managerie" Invite card 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Signature Series w/Ruby Dee 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Theatre Lover's Tour 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - "Glass Managerie" response card/Invitation 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Fellows Program Brochure 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - "On the Way Home" Invitation Response card 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - "Save the Arts" Brochure 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - 3 Play Holiday Special Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - Subscription info 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - Congressional ticket hotline card 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - 40th Anniversary special order form (Box Box 13)
  - Subscription Handbook 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - Subscription Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - Group Sales Brochure 1990-1991 (Box Box 13)
  - Deaf Series Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - 1990-1991 Anniversary Gala information (Box Box 13)
  - Employees Only stuffer 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Tele-sec stuffer 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Ushers discount 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - 1989-1990 Season pocket guide (Box Box 12)
  - "Midsummer's" Postcard 1989-1990 (Box Box 13)
  - Onstage publication Summer 1991 (Box Box 13)
  - Living Stage summer camp (Box Box 13)
  - Living Stage training program (Box Box 13)
  - Living Stage theatre benefit (Box Box 13)
  - The Creative Projects:Summer 1989 workshops (Box Box 13)
  - Living Stage Films Program Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - On Stage, Spring 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - 1990-1991 Season (Box Box 13)
  - Performance Workshops (Box Box 13)
  - residencies Brochure (Box Box 13)
  - Profile (publication) (Box Box 13)
  - On Stage, Winter 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - On Stage, Winter 1990 (Box Box 13)
  - On Stage, Spring 1991 (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation/Response Card "Midsummer Night's Dream" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "If You Think, It Is" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "The Brothers Karamazov" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Of Thee I Sing" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "The Way of the World" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard, "Of Thee I Sing" (Box Box 13)
  - flyer: "Love Letters" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard: "The Skin of our Teeth" (Box Box 13)
  - program: "Lover Letters" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard: "Avner the Eccentric" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard: "A History of African American Theatre" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard: "Stars and Stripes" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard:"Summer and Smoke", group sales (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard: "Summer and Smoke" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "The Skin of Our Teeth", May 12, 1993 (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: Tea and Conversation with Miss. Manners (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "The Way of the World" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "Of Thee I Sing" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "Its the Truth (if you think it is)" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "Its the Truth (if you think it is)" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation:"The Way of the World" (Box Box 13)
  - Brochure: "The VAT Pass" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard: "Richard III" (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard: "Blood Knot" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "Summer and Smoke" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "Summer and Smoke" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "The Brothers Karamazov" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "The Brothers Karamazov" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "The Skin of our Teeth" (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "Blood knot" (Box Box 13)
  - Playbill: "Avner the Eccentric" (Box Box 13)
  - Subscription Handbook 1991-1992 (Box Box 13)
  - Order Form: Three Play Package (Box Box 13)
  - Sales prices for 1992-1993 season (Box Box 13)
  - Program advertising rate info 1992-1993 (Box Box 13)
  - Printed materials 1992-1993 season (Box Box 13)
  - Program for Fichandler stage dedication (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "Antigone in NY" (Box Box 13)
  - Order form: special 40% off offer (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation: "Of Thee I Sing" (Box Box 13)
  - "On Stage" Vol. 4, #1 (Box Box 13)
  - "On Stage" Vol. 4, #2 (Box Box 13)
  - Buttons: "Win with Wintergreen" (Box Box 13)
  - "On Stage" Vol. 4, #3 (Box Box 13)
  - Reservation card: "Summer and Smoke" (Box Box 13)
  - cassette: "Merrily We Roll Along" (Box Box 13)
  - Budget - 40th Anniv. gala (Box Box 14)
  - Final figures - 40th Anniv. gala (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. photo exibit (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. press kit (Box Box 14)
  - book (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. council (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. honorary committee (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. White House correspondence (Box Box 14)
  - letters (Box Box 14)
  - Press letters (Box Box 14)
  - Timetable/deadlines (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. Invitation card (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. in-kind donations (Box Box 14)
  - Table sales target (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. guild/dinner committee (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. meeting minutes (Box Box 14)
  - Site arrangements (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. table sales (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. script for presentation (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. gala gifts report (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. regrets acceptances (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. salzo kit (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. gala funds (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. seating requests (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. table sales confirmation letters (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. general information (Box Box 14)
  - Underwriting (Box Box 14)
  - Gala program transcripts (Box Box 14)
  - Reception (Box Box 14)
  - Programs (Box Box 14)
  - Program credits (Box Box 14)
  - Program (Box Box 14)
  - Invitation and Program design (Box Box 14)
  - multi-media Program (Box Box 14)
  - 40th Anniv. donated hotel accommodations (Box Box 14)
  - Ads. 1973-1974 (Box Box 15)
  - Ads. 1971-1972 (Box Box 15)
  - Ads. 1970-1971 (Box Box 15)
  - Ads. 1969-1970 (Box Box 15)
  - Ads. 1968-1969 (Box Box 15)
  - ads. 1954-1955 (Box Box 15)
  - Ad. in the Daily Rag (Box Box 15)
  - Ads. 1976 (Box Box 15)
  - ads. 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - Tearsheet files 1977-1978 (Box Box 15)
  - Insertion orders (Box Box 15)
  - Playtime (Box Box 15)
  - Ads. 1975-1976 (Box Box 15)
  - ABC Ads. 1974-1975 (Box Box 15)
  - Tom's picture Ads. 1967-1968 (Box Box 15)
  - Misc. Ads. 1963-1964 (Box Box 15)
  - Playtime Ads. 1963-1964 (Box Box 15)
  - This Week Ads. 1963-1964 (Box Box 15)
  - Washington star and post Ads. (Box Box 15)
  - Star/News (Box Box 15)
  - Ads book 1972-1973 (Box Box 15)
  - Washington Star Ads. 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - Washington Post Ads. 1976-1978 (Box Box 15)
  - The Vagabond Players (Box Box 15)
  - Ads. 1961-1962 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads. 1961-1962 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads 1956-1958 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads. 1967-1969 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads 1962-1963 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads. 1960-1961 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads. 1966-1967 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads 1966-1967 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads. 1965-1966 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads. 1958-1959 (Box Box 16)
  - Ads. 1963-1964 (Box Box 13)
  - Israel (Box Box 16)
  - photos from hippodrome (Box Box 16)
  - photos from hippodrome (Box Box 16)
  - photos from hippodrome (Box Box 16)
  - Site map (Box Box 16)
  - Graphics (Box Box 16)
  - Arena Stage history (Box Box 17)
  - Tony Award (Box Box 17)
  - Official recognitions (Box Box 17)
  - Premieres (Box Box 17)
  - Foreign language articles (Box Box 17)
  - Architecture articles (Box Box 17)
  - General Articles 1950-1959 (Box Box 17)
  - General Articles 1960-1969 (Box Box 17)
  - General Articles 1980 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. Playbills/Programs (Box Box 17)
  - Living Stage Misc. info (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotional material 1959-1960 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1961-1962 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1957-1958 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1958-1959 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1960-1961 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1961-1962 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotions, 1962-1963 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1963-1964 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1964-1965 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1965-1966 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1966-1967 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1967-1968 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1968-1969 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1970-1971 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1971-1972 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1972-1973 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1973-1974 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1974-1975 (Box Box 17)
  - Misc. promotion 1975-1976 (Box Box 17)
  - invite samples 1981-1982 (Box Box 18)
  - The Playwrights Carousel of New Plays (Box Box 18)
  - 18 promotional cards (Box Box 18)
  - March 1981 press packet (Box Box 18)
  - Arena Stage Angels fund raising auction (Box Box 18)
  - Invitations 1984-1985 season (Box Box 18)
  - 30th Anniv. promotional material (Box Box 18)
  - Invitations: 1986-1987 season (Box Box 18)
  - Invitations: 1983-1984 season (Box Box 18)
  - Programs: 1982-1983 season (Box Box 18)
  - Opening night invites 1982-1983 (Box Box 18)
  - Programs: 1981-1982 season (Box Box 18)
  - P.P. Misc. (Box Box 18)
  - Misc. (Box Box 18)
  - 40 Years - A Great Stage of Life (Box Box 18)
  - Press Releases (Box Box 18)
  - Invitations: 1985-1986 season (Box Box 18)
  - Brochures Misc. seasons (Box Box 18)
  - Discount ticket mailings (Box Box 18)
  - Gala opening material (Box Box 18)
  - Events (Box Box 18)
  - Living Stage (Box Box 18)
  - Subscriber to ASA (Box Box 18)
  - 1986 calendar (Box Box 18)
  - Annual Reports: 1979-1983 (Box Box 18)
  - Annual Report: 1983-1991 (Box Box 18)
  - America's Arena (Box Box 18)
  - America's Arena (Box Box 18)
  - Misc. (Box Box 18)
  - Subscription Envelopes (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "Mrs. Klein" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "A Wonderful Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "A Wonderful Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "A Wonderful Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Reservation card: "The School for Wives" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "Trinidad Sisters" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "The Visit" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "Yerma" (Box Box 19)
  - subscription letter: 33% off ticket price (Box Box 19)
  - after deadline, subscription renewal letter (Box Box 19)
  - Subscription letter (Box Box 19)
  - Reservation card: "Trinidad Sisters" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "Mrs. Klein" (Box Box 19)
  - Reservation card: "Trinidad Sisters" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "The School for Wives" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "The Time of Your Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitations: "The Time of Your Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "The Time of You Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "Jar the Floor" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "Jar the Floor" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "Jar the Floor" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "The School for Wives" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: " Jar the Floor" (Box Box 19)
  - Response cards: "The Time of Your Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Response card: "Jar the Floor" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "The School of Wives" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "The School for Wives" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "The Father" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "The Father" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "The Visit" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "Love or Marriage" (Box Box 19)
  - Congressional Hispanic Caucus special Invitation to "Yerma" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "A Wonderful Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "On Borrowed Time" (Box Box 19)
  - Info packet on the AT and T presentation of "A Wonderful Life" (Box Box 19)
  - Brochure: Playquest at Arena Stage (Box Box 19)
  - Subscription Handbook: 1993-1994 season (Box Box 19)
  - Brochure: 1994-1995 season subscription (Box Box 19)
  - Brochure: "A Community Carol" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "The Skull Beneath the Smile" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "A Community Carol" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "Twelfth Night" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "A Room of One's Own" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "Dancing at Lughnasa" (Box Box 19)
  - Brochure: "The Revengers Comedies" (Box Box 19)
  - Postcard: "The Price" (Box Box 19)
  - Brochure: 4,5 or 6 Play packages (Box Box 19)
  - Booklet: "The Revenge of the Comedies" (Box Box 19)
  - Booklet: "A Small World" (Box Box 19)
  - Booklet: "A Room of One's Own" (Box Box 19)
  - Booklet: "A Community Carol" (Box Box 19)
  - Booklet: "The Price" (Box Box 19)
  - Booklet: "Dancing at Lughnasa" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "Twelfth Night" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitation: "A Room of One's Own" (Box Box 19)
  - Invitations: "Dancing at Lughnasa" (Box Box 19)